A Guide to the Nelson A. Rockefeller Gubernatorial records, Diane Van Wie, Series 34 FA373
Rockefeller Archive Center
- Miscellaneous Files, 1958-1973; 11; 31 document box(es)
  - Annual Message to the Legislature, January 18, 1972 (Box 144, Folder 3963)
  - Annual Budget Message, 1973-1974 (Box 144, Folder 3964)
  - Inauguration, January 2, 1967 (Box 144, Folder 3965)
  - Inaugural Message Drafts, 1971 (Box 144, Folder 3966)
  - Inaugural Message Drafts, 1971 (Box 144, Folder 3967)
  - Questions from Albany Press Conference, July 31, 1969 (Box 144, Folder 3968)
  - Coordinating Committee on the South Mall Project - Progress Report, January 14, 1969 (Box 144, Folder 3969)
    Related Archival Materials note
    See also Box 130
  - Coordinating Committee on the South Mall Project - Progress Report, May 13, 1969 (Box 144, Folder 3970)
  - Nelson A. Rockefeller Biography, August 1970 (Box 144, Folder 3971)
  - Miscellaneous Memos Left in Original Order (Folder A), 1961-1965 (Box 145, Folder 3972)
  - Miscellaneous Memos Left in Original Order (Folder B), 1961-1965 (Box 145, Folder 3973)
  - Chairmanship Letters, February 18, 1964 (Box 145, Folder 3974)
  - Chairmanship Letters - New Hampshire, March 11, 1964 (Box 145, Folder 3975)
  - Chairmanship Letters, February 26, 1964 (Box 145, Folder 3976)
  - West Virginia Primary List, March 30, 1964 (Box 145, Folder 3977)
  - Chairmanship Letters - Maine, April 3, 1964 (Box 145, Folder 3978)
  - Chairmanship Letters - Maine, April 6, 1964 (Box 145, Folder 3979)
  - Chairmanship Letters - Maine, April 8, 1964 (Box 145, Folder 3980)
  - Massachusetts Delegate File, April 30, 1964 (Box 145, Folder 3981)
  - Chairmanship Letters - Oregon, May 4, 1964 (Box 145, Folder 3982)
  - Maine Delegate List, May 4, 1964 (Box 145, Folder 3983)
  - Vermont Delegates, May 20, 1964 (Box 145, Folder 3984)
  - Oregon Thank You Letter Drafts (List of Names), undated (Box 145, Folder 3985)
  - Lake County Commission for Nomination of Nelson Rockefeller for President (Committee List) - Oregon, undated (Box 145, Folder 3986)
  - Oregon Labor Committee, May 6, 1964 (Box 145, Folder 3987)
  - Oregon Businessmen's Committee, May 15, 1964 (Box 145, Folder 3988)
  - Oregon Speakers Committee (List of Names), undated (Box 145, Folder 3989)
  - Pennsylvania Delegates, May 14, 1964 (Box 145, Folder 3990)
  - Rhode Island Delegates, May 13, 1964 (Box 145, Folder 3991)
  - Delaware Delegates, May 6, 1964 (Box 145, Folder 3992)
  - District of Columbia Delegates, May 6, 1964 (Box 145, Folder 3993)
  - Thank You Letters- Drafts and Lists - California, undated (Box 145, Folder 3994)
  - Political Letters Ratio, undated (Box 145, Folder 3995)
  - Miscellaneous Flat Lists, February 1964 (Box 145, Folder 3996)
  - Personnel Lists - "Rockefeller for President", undated (Box 145, Folder 3997)
  - Releases and Memos - Republican Party, August 1964 (Box 145, Folder 3998)
  - Form Letters - 1964 Campaign (Box 145, Folder 3999)
  - Drafts for NAR Signature, 1963-1964 (Box 145, Folder 4000)
  - "Rockefeller for President National Campaign Committee", 1964 (Box 146, Folder 4001)
  - Thank You Letters, for Staff and Campaign Workers, July 24, 1964 (Box 146, Folder 4002)
  - Drafts of Letters to Winners of Primaries, also Lists of Names, 1964 (Box 146, Folder 4003)
  - List of Names (Holding for Harriet) Rockefeller County Chairmen, 1964 (Box 146, Folder 4004)
  - Hold Outs 1964 Campaign (Box 146, Folder 4005)
  - New York State Letters and Memos from Wilma Rogalin, Political, 1963-1964 (Box 146, Folder 4006)
  - New York State Memos Sent by Wilma Rogalin to State Committee Men, 1964 (Box 146, Folder 4007)
  - New York State Samuel Hausman Report, 1962 (Box 146, Folder 4008)
  - New York State re: State Chairmen, January 5, 1962 (Box 146, Folder 4009)
  - New York State Material Sent to Chairmen and Vice Chairmen, 1963 (Box 146, Folder 4010)
  - New York State Newspaper Clippings, 1963 (Box 146, Folder 4011)
  - New York State New York Report, 1963 (Box 146, Folder 4012)
  - Legislation Court Reorganization, March 26, 1963 (Box 146, Folder 4013)
  - Legislation Economic Growth, undated (Box 146, Folder 4014)
  - Legislation Fees, 1963 (Box 146, Folder 4015)
  - Legislation Labor Law, undated (Box 146, Folder 4016)
  - Legislation Local Government, 1963 (Box 146, Folder 4017)
  - Legislation Mental Hygiene, January 30, 1963 (Box 146, Folder 4018)
  - Legislation Narcotics, March 1, 1963 (Box 146, Folder 4019)
  - Legislation Public Housing, undated (Box 146, Folder 4020)
  - Legislation Payment of Temporary Unemployment Compensation (TUC), undated (Box 146, Folder 4021)
  - Legislation School Financing, March 13, 1963 (Box 146, Folder 4022)
  - Legislation Space Center, 1963-1964 (Box 146, Folder 4023)
  - Legislation State Recreation Council, March 20, 1963 (Box 146, Folder 4024)
  - Legislation Tri-State Transportation Commission, undated (Box 146, Folder 4025)
  - Legislation Water Supply Planning Assistance, 1963-1964 (Box 146, Folder 4026)
  - Mary K. Boland Press Reaction to Maine Trip, March 1962 (Box 146, Folder 4027)
  - Mary K. Boland Research Iran, November 27, 1961 (Box 146, Folder 4028)
  - Mary K. Boland Research Nevada, undated (Box 146, Folder 4029)
  - National Letters and Memos to Governor, 1963-1964 (Box 146, Folder 4030)
  - National Republican Club, 1963 (Box 146, Folder 4031)
  - National Nuclear Testing, February 10, 1963 (Box 146, Folder 4032)
  - National Statement of Joint Senate-House Republican Leadership, 1963 (Box 146, Folder 4033)
  - National Releases from the Women's National Republican Club, 1963 (Box 146, Folder 4034)
  - National Radio and Television, 1963 (Box 146, Folder 4035)
  - National Newspaper Clippings, 1963-1964 (Box 146, Folder 4036)
  - National - Republican National Committee, 1963-1965 (Box 147, Folder 4037)
  - New York State Letters and Memos to the Governor, 1963-1964 (Box 147, Folder 4038)
  - National Kennedy Information, 1963 (Box 147, Folder 4039)
  - "They Said It and News" - New York Republican State Committee, 1965 (Box 147, Folder 4040)
  - Greeting to Thomas J. Hollywood Catholics for Latin America, January 15, 1964 (Box 147, Folder 4041)
  - Congressional Delegation Meeting, February 24, 1965 (Box 147, Folder 4042)
  - Tentative Attendance Board of Directors Meeting Empire State Chamber of Commerce, February 3, 1965 (Box 147, Folder 4043)
  - Ditchley Foundation (Britain), 1963 (Box 147, Folder 4044)
  - Financing Better Transportation for the People of New York State, September 1971 (Box 147, Folder 4045)
  - Maps of Congressional Districts, February 1968; 13 maps (Box 161, Folder 4177)
- Executive Chamber Correspondence, 1970-1973; 12; 13 document box(es)
  The letters are arranged alphabetically by last name.
  This subseries consists of miscellaneous outgoing letters, such as letters of support and sympathy. The letters are unsigned carbon copies.
  - Personal (A), 1970-1973 (Box 148, Folder 4046)
  - Personal (A), 1970-1973 (Box 148, Folder 4047)
  - Personal (Ag), 1970-1973 (Box 148, Folder 4048)
  - Personal (Am), 1970-1973 (Box 148, Folder 4049)
  - Personal (As), 1970-1973 (Box 148, Folder 4050)
  - Personal (B), 1970-1973 (Box 148, Folder 4051)
  - Personal (Bar), 1970-1973 (Box 148, Folder 4052)
  - Personal (Be), 1970-1973 (Box 148, Folder 4053)
  - Personal (Ber), 1970-1973 (Box 148, Folder 4054)
  - Personal (Bi), 1970-1973 (Box 148, Folder 4055)
  - Personal (Bo), 1970-1973 (Box 149, Folder 4056)
  - Personal (Br), 1970-1973 (Box 149, Folder 4057)
  - Personal (Bu), 1970-1973 (Box 149, Folder 4058)
  - Personal (C), 1970-1973 (Box 149, Folder 4059)
  - Personal (Car), 1970-1973 (Box 149, Folder 4060)
  - Personal (Ce), 1970-1973 (Box 149, Folder 4061)
  - Personal (Ci), 1970-1973 (Box 149, Folder 4062)
  - Personal (Co), 1970-1973 (Box 150, Folder 4063)
  - Personal (Cor), 1970-1973 (Box 150, Folder 4064)
  - Personal (Cu), 1970-1973 (Box 150, Folder 4065)
  - Personal (D), 1970-1973 (Box 150, Folder 4066)
  - Personal (De), 1970-1973 (Box 150, Folder 4067)
  - Personal (Dem), 1970-1973 (Box 150, Folder 4068)
  - Personal (Di), 1970-1973 (Box 150, Folder 4069)
  - Personal (Do), 1970-1973 (Box 150, Folder 4070)
  - Personal (Du), 1970-1973 (Box 151, Folder 4071)
  - Personal (E), 1970-1973 (Box 151, Folder 4072)
  - Personal (Em), 1970-1973 (Box 151, Folder 4073)
  - Personal (Er), 1970-1973 (Box 151, Folder 4074)
  - Personal (F), 1970-1973 (Box 151, Folder 4075)
  - Personal (Fe), 1970-1973 (Box 151, Folder 4076)
  - Personal (Fi), 1970-1973 (Box 151, Folder 4077)
  - Personal (Fo), 1970-1973 (Box 151, Folder 4078)
  - Personal (Fu), 1970-1973 (Box 151, Folder 4079)
  - Personal (G), 1970-1973 (Box 151, Folder 4080)
  - Personal (Ge), 1970-1973 (Box 152, Folder 4081)
  - Personal (Gi), 1970-1973 (Box 152, Folder 4082)
  - Personal (Go), 1970-1973 (Box 152, Folder 4083)
  - Personal (Gr), 1970-1973 (Box 152, Folder 4084)
  - Personal (Gu), 1970-1973 (Box 152, Folder 4085)
  - Personal (H), 1970-1973 (Box 152, Folder 4086)
  - Personal (Har), 1970-1973 (Box 152, Folder 4087)
  - Personal (He), 1970-1973 (Box 152, Folder 4088)
  - Personal (Hi), 1970-1973 (Box 153, Folder 4089)
  - Personal (Ho), 1970-1973 (Box 153, Folder 4090)
  - Personal (Hol), 1970-1973 (Box 153, Folder 4091)
  - Personal (Hu), 1970-1973 (Box 153, Folder 4092)
  - Personal (I), 1970-1973 (Box 153, Folder 4093)
  - Personal (Im), 1970-1973 (Box 153, Folder 4094)
  - Personal (J), 1970-1973 (Box 153, Folder 4095)
  - Personal (Je), 1970-1973 (Box 153, Folder 4096)
  - Personal (Ji), 1970-1973 (Box 153, Folder 4097)
  - Personal (Jo), 1970-1973 (Box 153, Folder 4098)
  - Personal (Ju), 1970-1973 (Box 153, Folder 4099)
  - Personal (K), 1970-1973 (Box 153, Folder 4100)
  - Personal (Ke), 1970-1973 (Box 153, Folder 4101)
  - Personal (Ki), 1970-1973 (Box 153, Folder 4102)
  - Personal (Kl), 1970-1973 (Box 154, Folder 4103)
  - Personal (Ko), 1970-1973 (Box 154, Folder 4104)
  - Personal (Ku), 1970-1973 (Box 154, Folder 4105)
  - Personal (L), 1970-1973 (Box 154, Folder 4106)
  - Personal (Lar), 1970-1973 (Box 154, Folder 4107)
  - Personal (Le), 1970-1973 (Box 154, Folder 4108)
  - Personal (Leo), 1970-1973 (Box 154, Folder 4109)
  - Personal (Li), 1970-1973 (Box 154, Folder 4110)
  - Personal (Lo), 1970-1973 (Box 154, Folder 4111)
  - Personal (Lu), 1970-1973 (Box 155, Folder 4112)
  - Personal (M), 1970-1973 (Box 155, Folder 4113)
  - Personal (Mar), 1970-1973 (Box 155, Folder 4114)
  - Personal (Mc), 1970-1973 (Box 155, Folder 4115)
  - Personal (Me), 1970-1973 (Box 155, Folder 4116)
  - Personal (Mi), 1970-1973 (Box 155, Folder 4117)
  - Personal (Mo), 1970-1973 (Box 156, Folder 4118)
  - Personal (Mor), 1970-1973 (Box 156, Folder 4119)
  - Personal (Mu), 1970-1973 (Box 156, Folder 4120)
  - Personal (N), 1970-1973 (Box 156, Folder 4121)
  - Personal (Ne), 1970-1973 (Box 156, Folder 4122)
  - Personal (Ni), 1970-1973 (Box 156, Folder 4123)
  - Personal (No), 1970-1973 (Box 156, Folder 4124)
  - Personal (Nu), 1970-1973 (Box 156, Folder 4125)
  - Personal (O), 1970-1973 (Box 156, Folder 4126)
  - Personal (Om), 1970-1973 (Box 156, Folder 4127)
  - Personal (Os), 1970-1973 (Box 156, Folder 4128)
  - Personal (P), 1970-1973 (Box 156, Folder 4129)
  - Personal (Pe), 1970-1973 (Box 157, Folder 4130)
  - Personal (Pi), 1970-1973 (Box 157, Folder 4131)
  - Personal (Po), 1970-1973 (Box 157, Folder 4132)
  - Personal (Pu), 1970-1973 (Box 157, Folder 4133)
  - Personal (Qu), 1970-1973 (Box 157, Folder 4134)
  - Personal (R), 1970-1973 (Box 157, Folder 4135)
  - Personal (Re), 1970-1973 (Box 157, Folder 4136)
  - Personal (Ri), 1970-1973 (Box 157, Folder 4137)
  - Personal (Ro), 1970-1973 (Box 157, Folder 4138)
  - Personal (Roe), 1970-1973 (Box 157, Folder 4139)
  - Personal (Ru), 1970-1973 (Box 158, Folder 4140)
  - Personal (S), 1970-1973 (Box 158, Folder 4141)
  - Personal (Sch), 1970-1973 (Box 158, Folder 4142)
  - Personal (Scho), 1970-1973 (Box 158, Folder 4143)
  - Personal (Se), 1970-1973 (Box 158, Folder 4144)
  - Personal (Sh), 1970-1973 (Box 158, Folder 4145)
  - Personal (Shl), 1970-1973 (Box 158, Folder 4146)
  - Personal (Si), 1970-1973 (Box 158, Folder 4147)
  - Personal (Sl), 1970-1973 (Box 158, Folder 4148)
  - Personal (So), 1970-1973 (Box 159, Folder 4149)
  - Personal (St), 1970-1973 (Box 159, Folder 4150)
  - Personal (Sti), 1970-1973 (Box 159, Folder 4151)
  - Personal (Su), 1970-1973 (Box 159, Folder 4152)
  - Personal (T), 1970-1973 (Box 159, Folder 4153)
  - Personal (Te), 1970-1973 (Box 159, Folder 4154)
  - Personal (Ti), 1970-1973 (Box 159, Folder 4155)
  - Personal (To), 1970-1973 (Box 159, Folder 4156)
  - Personal (Tu), 1970-1973 (Box 159, Folder 4157)
  - Personal (U), 1970-1973 (Box 159, Folder 4158)
  - Personal (Um), 1970-1973 (Box 159, Folder 4159)
  - Personal (Us), 1970-1973 (Box 159, Folder 4160)
  - Personal (V), 1970-1973 (Box 159, Folder 4161)
  - Personal (Ve), 1970-1973 (Box 159, Folder 4162)
  - Personal (Vi), 1970-1973 (Box 159, Folder 4163)
  - Personal (Vu), 1970-1973 (Box 160, Folder 4164)
  - Personal (W), 1970-1973 (Box 160, Folder 4165)
  - Personal (War), 1970-1973 (Box 160, Folder 4166)
  - Personal (We), 1970-1973 (Box 160, Folder 4167)
  - Personal (Wh), 1970-1973 (Box 160, Folder 4168)
  - Personal (Wi), 1970-1973 (Box 160, Folder 4169)
  - Personal (Win), 1970-1973 (Box 160, Folder 4170)
  - Personal (Wo), 1970-1973 (Box 160, Folder 4171)
  - Personal (Wu), 1970-1973 (Box 160, Folder 4172)
  - Personal (X), 1970-1973 (Box 160, Folder 4173)
  - Personal (Y), 1970-1973 (Box 160, Folder 4174)
  - Personal (Z), 1970-1973 (Box 160, Folder 4175)